Hey, GuyPo. Tessl has been helping agents use open- source libraries much much better with
context. Uh, people have known that for a long time now, but we've recently introduced evals.
What is an eval? An eval is basically a coding scenario that demonstrates that an agent can
perform some action, a skill or use a library on it. Uh, and typically includes the coding
scenario itself and some scorecard or some means of judging how well the agent performed. So,
you can run that with and without the change. And when we say Tessl's released an eval feature,
what does that mean? What does it look like to a user? It means that we took a sample of over 300
libraries from our 10,000 that we support. Uh, and we've created with agents these 10 coding
scenarios for them to run scorecards for all of those. Uh, and then we've run them. We've
run them with Claude. We support a variety of them and we've shared the results. So you can
now just sort of see them on tessl.io/registry and explore what does that even look like and
what are the actual kind of level of help that you can expect. Awesome. And why is this important to
developers who are using agents? First of all, you know, it's important to us to sort of make
sure that our context is actually valuable. Um, and we've already sort of seen that help. Two
is when someone tells us uh this helps agents, we should, you know, get in the habit of asking
show me the data and get evals. So, we hope we're promoting that trend. And lastly is we think this
uh ability to run evals and shape evals is a skill that developers will need to have
for their own content. Uh, and so we're hoping there's a bit of a learning moment for that. So,
show me the data. Do you have any examples? Uh there's a lot of data you can find on the
registry. Uh a few favorite examples we see how for pypi's async standard lib for instance
uh we go from about 25% success rate to about 84%. For Webpack bundle analyzer we go from about 80%
to about 99% success. And then we only published the percentage of the evaluation of how well
uh can the agent sort of use this API. But what we've also seen is that we often times make agents
much much more efficient. you know, often times twice as fast or fewer tokens. So, we're going
to publish that data soon as well. And that's a huge deal. Hey, if you like what you're hearing,
why don't you head over to tessl.io/registry where you can find all the context as well as the evals.